<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nos derniers articles on SUPERGREEN | Créateur de sites web écolos</title>
    <link>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nos derniers articles on SUPERGREEN | Créateur de sites web écolos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <copyright>Conçu par [Themefisher](https://themefisher.com/) &amp; Développé par [Gethugothemes](https://gethugothemes.com/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>15 façons de rendre votre site web plus écolo</title>
      <link>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Over the past couple of years, we’ve talked a lot about the carbon footprint of websites. The carbon impact of the web is largely caused by electricity use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comment définir un budget de poids de page pour un site Web plus écologique et plus rapide</title>
      <link>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-4/</guid>
      <description>Since I was in my teens I’ve been interested in both sustainability and design. When I co-founded Wholegrain Digital with Vineeta over a decade ago, it was natural that I wanted the business to embody my interests and values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo vs WordPress : le pour et le contre des générateurs de sites statiques</title>
      <link>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-3/</guid>
      <description>What is a static site generator? A static site generator lets you generate a static website using data and templates. A static website is pre-rendered: all the files (HTML, CSS, Javascript and images) exist as is, and do not need to be processed on the server level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>L&#39;éthique dans la conception de sites web</title>
      <link>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:22:16 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djangossoul.github.io/blog/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Ethics in web design aren’t immediately obvious or at the forefront of the industry, but I believe now more than ever, ethics are paramount to digital experience design.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>